Unicode Fonts for Ancient Scripts
http://users.teilar.gr/~g1951d/

George Douros
g1951d@teilar.gr

2010

In lieu of a licence:
Fonts in ‘Unicode Fonts for Ancient Scripts’ are offered free for any use; they may be opened, edited, modified, regenerated, posted, packaged and redistributed.

_____________________________
Symbola.otf
Version 6.01
Symbola is not a merchandise.

Symbola covers the following scripts and symbols supported by The Unicode Standard 6.0:
Basic Latin, IPA Extensions, Spacing Modifier Letters, Combining Diacritical Marks, Greek and Coptic, Cyrillic, Cyrillic Supplement, General Punctuation, Superscripts and Subscripts, Currency Symbols, Combining Diacritical Marks for Symbols, Letterlike Symbols, Number Forms, Arrows, Mathematical Operators, Miscellaneous Technical, Control Pictures, Optical Character Recognition, Box Drawing, Block Elements, Geometric Shapes, Miscellaneous Symbols, Dingbats, Miscellaneous Mathematical Symbols-A, Supplemental Arrows-A, Supplemental Arrows-B, Miscellaneous Mathematical Symbols-B, Supplemental Mathematical Operators, Miscellaneous Symbols and Arrows, Supplemental Punctuation, Yijing Hexagram Symbols, Combining Half Marks, Specials, Byzantine Musical Symbols, Musical Symbols, Ancient Greek Musical Notation, Tai Xuan Jing Symbols, Counting Rod Numerals, Mathematical Alphanumeric Symbols, Mahjong Tiles, Domino Tiles, Playing Cards, Miscellaneous Symbols And Pictographs, Emoticons, Transport And Map Symbols, Alchemical Symbols and characters of occasional mathematical interest: Eastern Arabic-Indic digits (06F0...06F9), the Hiragana letter 306E, the ideograph 4E2D, standardized mathematical variants et al.

>>>>	*ERRATA*: The following glyphs are NOT ENCODED in Unicode.

20F1	◌⃱	ENCLOSING ROUNDED SQUARE
20F2	◌⃲	ENCLOSING RIGHTWARDS WHITE SHORT ARROW
20F3	◌⃳	ENCLOSED DOUBLE ROUNDED SQUARE

23F4	⏴	MENU INVOCATION
23F5	⏵	PARTIAL BACKWARD DELETE

2427	␧	SYMBOL FOR EN SPACE
2428	␨	SYMBOL FOR EM SPACE
2429	␩	SYMBOL FOR THREE-PER-EM SPACE
242A	␪	SYMBOL FOR FOUR-PER-EM SPACE
242B	␫	SYMBOL FOR SIX-PER-EM SPACE
242C	␬	SYMBOL FOR FIGURE SPACE
242D	␭	SYMBOL FOR PUNCTUATION SPACE
242E	␮	SYMBOL FOR THIN OR NARROW SPACE
242F	␯	SYMBOL FOR HAIR SPACE
2430	␰	SYMBOL FOR ZERO WIDTH SPACE
2431	␱	SYMBOL FOR MEDIUM MATHEMATICAL SPACE
2432	␲	SYMBOL FOR NARROW NO-BREAK SPACE
2433	␳	SYMBOL FOR SOFT HYPHEN
2434	␴	SYMBOL FOR NON-BREAKING HYPHEN
2435	␵	SYMBOL FOR NON-STOPPING DOT
2436	␶	SYMBOL FOR LINE SEPARATOR
2437	␷	SYMBOL FOR PARAGRAPH SEPARATOR
2438	␸	SYMBOL FOR ZERO WIDTH NON-JOINER
2439	␹	SYMBOL FOR ZERO WITDH JOINER
243A	␺	SYMBOL FOR WORD JOINER
243B	␻	SYMBOL FOR COMBINING GRAPHEME JOINER
243C	␼	SYMBOL FOR LEFT-TO-RIGHT MARK
243D	␽	SYMBOL FOR RIGHT-TO-LEFT MARK

27CB	⟋	MATHEMATICAL RISING DIAGONAL
27CD	⟍	MATHEMATICAL FALLING DIAGONAL

2B4D	⭍	PAIR OF BRACKETS WITH OUTWARDS ARROWS
2B4E	⭎	LEFTWARDS ARROW THROUGH LEFT BRACKET
2B4F	⭏	RIGHTWARDS ARROW THROUGH RIGHT BRACKET

2B5A	⭚	LEFTWARDS ARROW FROM BAR TO BAR
2B5B	⭛	UPWARDS ARROW FROM BAR TO BAR
2B5C	⭜	RIGHTWARDS ARROW FROM BAR TO BAR
2B5D	⭝	DOWNWARDS ARROW FROM BAR TO BAR
2B5E	⭞	LEFTWARDS ARROW FROM BAR TO BRACKET
2B5F	⭟	RIGHTWARDS ARROW FROM BAR TO BRACKET
2B60	⭠	LEFTWARDS SHORT ARROW FROM LONG BAR TO SHORT AND LONG BAR
2B61	⭡	UPWARDS SHORT ARROW FROM LONG BAR TO SHORT AND LONG BAR
2B62	⭢	RIGHTWARDS SHORT ARROW FROM LONG BAR TO SHORT AND LONG BAR
2B63	⭣	DOWNWARDS SHORT ARROW FROM LONG BAR TO SHORT AND LONG BAR
2B64	⭤	LEFTWARDS WHITE DOUBLE ARROW
2B65	⭥	LEFTWARDS ARROW WITH SHORT DOWNWARDS START
2B66	⭦	RIGHTWARDS WHITE DOUBLE ARROW
2B67	⭧	DOWNWARDS WHITE DOUBLE ARROW

2B70	⭰	SPACE SELECT SYMBOL
2B71	⭱	WHITE SQUARE WITH RAYS
2B72	⭲	VERTICAL HALF WHITE SQUARE WITH RIGHT RAYS
2B73	⭳	HORIZONTAL STROKE APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B74	⭴	DIAGONAL SLASH APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B75	⭵	OVERLAID TILDE APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B76	⭶	HOOK BELOW APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B77	⭷	HOOK ABOVE APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B78	⭸	HOOK APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B79	⭹	SUPERSCRIPT APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B7A	⭺	SUBSCRIPT APPLICATOR SYMBOL
2B7B	⭻	SUPERSCRIPT AND SUBSCRIPT APPLICATOR SYMBOL

2E32	⸲	TURNED COMMA
2E35	⸵	TURNED SEMICOLON
2E36	⸶	DAGGER WITH LEFT GUARD
2E37	⸷	DAGGER WITH RIGHT GUARD
2E38	⸸	TURNED DAGGER
2E39	⸹	TOP HALF SECTION SIGN
2E3A	⸺	TWO-EM DASH
2E3B	⸻	THREE-EM DASH
2E3C	⸼	RAISED DOT
2E3D	⸽	RAISED COMMA
2E3E	⸾	MIDDLE COMMA
2E3F	⸿	SMALL RAISED DAGGER

1F540	🕀	CIRCLED CROSS POMMY
1F541	🕁	CROSS POMMY WITH HALF-CIRCLE BELOW
1F542	🕂	CROSS POMMY
1F543	🕃	NOTCHED LEFT SEMICIRCLE WITH THREE DOTS
1F544	🕄	NOTCHED RIGHT SEMICIRCLE WITH THREE DOTS

1F600	😀	GRINNING FACE
1F611	😑	EXPRESSIONLESS FACE
1F615	😕	CONFUSED FACE
1F617	😗	KISSING FACE
1F619	😙	KISSING FACE WITH SMILING EYES
1F61B	😛	FACE WITH STUCK-OUT TONGUE
1F61F	😟	WORRIED FACE
1F626	😦	FROWNING FACE WITH OPEN MOUTH
1F627	😧	ANGUISHED FACE
1F62C	😬	GRIMACING FACE
1F62E	😮	FACE WITH OPEN MOUTH
1F62F	😯	HUSHED FACE
1F634	😴	SLEEPING FACE

>>>>	VARIANTS: Standardized Mathematical Variants are offered as OpenType features and as independent glyphs in FFF80-FFF98. Glyphs FFF99-FFF9C are alternates of 210E, 210F, 2133, 2134.

FFF99	󿾙	PLANCK CONSTANT, alternate
FFF9A	󿾚	PLANCK CONSTANT OVER TWO PI, alternate
FFF9B	󿾛	SCRIPT CAPITAL M, alternate
FFF9C	󿾜	SCRIPT SMALL O, alternate